Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office for Local Government Subject File, 1933-1973; 5; 10 cubic ft.
  - Reapportionment, Conference on, 1965 March 03 (Box 19 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Reapportionment - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 19 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Reapportionment - Court Decisions, Eight Counties, 1964-1968 (Box 19 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Reapportionment - General Information, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 19 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 13-14)
  - Reapportionment - Information Bulletins and OLG Publications, 1964-1969; 2 folders (Box 19 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 15-16)
  - Regents, Board of - Honorary Degrees Conferred By, 1964 (Box 19 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Reapportionment - Meetings with Speaker Travia, 1966 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Reapportionment - Report of the Joint Legislature Committee on, 1964-1965 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Regional Meetings, 1967 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1959-1961 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Reid, William - Honorary Dinner, 1964-1966 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 5)
  - Reorganization Plan for State Government, 1960 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 6)
  - Resource Material, 1964-1967 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Research Bank of State and Local Materials (Special Committee), 1964 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Revenue Sharing Program, 1969 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson, 1957 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson, 1958-1964 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson, 1958-1971 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson, 1965-1969 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 13)
  - Ronan, William J., 1959-1966 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Sales Tax, 1967 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 15)
  - School Boards Association, 1965-1971; 3 folders (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 16-18)
  - Sewer Study, 1960-1964; 3 folders (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 19-21)
  - Smart, Charlotte, 1964-1968 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 22)
  - State Aid, 1961-1970; 3 folders (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 23-25)
  - State Debt, 1968 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 26)
  - State & Local Officials - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 20 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 27)
  - State & Local Officials - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 1)
  - State & Local Officials - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 2)
  - State & Local Officials - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 3)
  - State & Local Officials - Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 4)
  - State Commission on Coordination of State Activities, 1960 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 5)
  - State Legislature Progress Reporter, 1966-1967 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 6)
  - States - General, 1965 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Student Orientation Program, 1962 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Suburban Town Conferences, 1962 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Suburban Town Government, 1961-1968; 3 folders (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 10-12)
  - Suburban Town Law Legislation, 1961-1962; 2 folders (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 13-14)
  - Taxation of State Lands, 1959-1962 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Tomkins County - Reorganization, 1968; Undated (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 16)
  - Tonawanda, 1966 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Town & County Officers Training School, 1966-1968 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Towns - General, 1960-1966 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Town Law, Revision of - Special Districts, 1965-1968 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee - Members as of 5/9/1968, 1969 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 21)
  - SUNY Cortland Workshop on State and Local Government and Politics, 1963 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Urban Affairs - Proposed Department of, 1967-1969 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 23)
  - Urban Aid, Mayor's Lindsay's Tax Sharing Plan, 1967-1968 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 24)
  - Urban Bill of Rights, 1968 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Urban Coalition, 1968-1969 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Urban Development Corporation, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 27-28)
  - Urban Renewal, 1960-1967 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Villages - General, 1940-1968 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 30)
  - Water Pollution, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 31-32)
  - Welfare, 1969 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 33)
  - Work Papers, 1959 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 34)
  - Workshop, 1965 (Box 21 (5-Office for Local Government Subject File), Folder 35)
- General Correspondence and Subject File, 1896-1978; 6; 6 cubic ft.
  This series consists of Moore's correspondence with various individuals and files related to subjects outside the scope of the Office for Local Government. Of particular note are a number of files regarding Moore's personal library (Moore was a rare book collector and donated much of his collection to various institutions), files on conservation, files on Moore's First World War service, a certificate of the legislative resolution mourning Moore's death in 1978, material regarding Moore's opposition to the New York State Lottery, extensive files of news clippings on Moore, an extensive file of photographs (beginning Box 6, Folder 21), and scrapbooks. Also of note is a collection of letters by Moore's predecessor as State Comptroller, James A. Roberts, which was presented to Moore by a rare book dealer of his acquaintance (Box 22, Folder 24.) The series is arranged alphabetically by correspondent and/or subject.
  - 1944 Presidential Campaign (Dewey vs. Roosevelt) - News Clippings (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 1)
  - A - Correspondence, 1955-1969 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Adirondack Hudson River Association, 1968 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Albany Mail, 1971 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Yeshiva University, 1954-1968 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 5)
  - American Christian College, 1973 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 6)
  - American Political Science Association, 1970-1972 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Anti-4% Sales Tax Committee, 1959 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 8)
  - B - General, 1958-1966 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1952-1965 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Board of Regents, 1971 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Books - Book Orders, 1963-1968; 2 folders (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 12-13)
  - Books - Donated to Office for Local Government, 1969-1970 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Books - Donated to the State University of New York, 1965 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Books - Donated to SUNY Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1962-1970 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 16)
  - Books - General, 1931-1969 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Books - General, 1955-1963 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Books - General, 1970-1972 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Books - Hammond, 1950-1960 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Books - Owned by FCM but to be Located, 1954-1963 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 21)
  - Books - Partial List of Rosalind's Books (Those Shipped from Buffalo 1964 or 1965), Undated (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Books - Scopes, John & Frank, 1945-1968 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 23)
  - Books - Scopes, John & Frank - Comptroller Roberts Letters, 1896 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 24)
  - Books - Tucker - State University, 1973 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Box Lists, 1957-1965 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Burns, John, 1969-1971 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 27)
  - C - General, 1954-1970 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 28)
  - Capitol Hill Club - Washington, 1953-1960 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Capitol Hill Club of Buffalo, 1968-1969 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 30)
  - "Carroll, Low, Beckrary [?] and Others", 1949-1953 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey, 1956-1963 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 32)
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1954-1968 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 33)
  - Clippings on Individuals, 1965-1967 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 34)
  - Commissions, 1944-1968 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 35)
  - Commission on Educational Finances, 1954 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 36)
  - Commission on School Buildings, 1953-1954 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 37)
  - Committee on Constitutional Tax & Debt Limitations & City - School Fiscal Relations, 1953-1959 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 38)
  - Comptroller's Office (State) - 150th Anniversary Dinner, 1947 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 39)
  - Comptroller's Office (State) - 150th Anniversary Dinner - Programs, 1947 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 40)
  - Comptroller's Office (State) - 150th Anniversary Dinner - Facsmile of First Comptroller's Report, 1947 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 41)
  - Conference of Mayors, 1955-1967 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 42)
  - Congratulatory Letters (Incoming & Outgoing), 1952 (Box 22 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 43)
  - Conservation, 1950-1952 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Conservation, 1952-1954 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Conservation, 1955-1957 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Conservation, 1958-1961 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Black River Regulating District, 1950 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 5)
  - Conservation Commission - Recommendations for, 1958 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Frank C. Moore on Panther Dam (Clippings), 1955 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Conservation - General, 1968 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Conservation - Indian Lake/Adirondack Mountains National Park, 1967 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Conservation - Wise Amendment, 1954 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Consumers' Union, 1972 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1967 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 13)
  - Council of State Governments, 1960-1962 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Council of State Governments, 1970 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Council of the Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 16)
  - D - General, 1966-1971 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Delta Chi Quarterly, 1920 March (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Desk Calendar, 1961 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Desk Calenday, 1969 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Desk Calendar, 1975 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 21)
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1942-1962 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Dewey, Governor Thomas E., 1943-1954 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 23)
  - Dewey, Thomas - Christmas Card, Undated (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 24)
  - Dillon, Vandewater & Moore - Legal Documents, 1934-1943 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Disposition of Frank C. Moore Papers, 1968-1969 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Douglass, Robert R., 1972 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 27)
  - Downey, Martha, 1965 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 28)
  - Dowsey, James L., 1958 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Drugs & Drug Abuse, Undated (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 30)
  - E - General, 1953-1969 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Economic Education Bulletin, 1972-1974 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 32)
  - Educational Television, Undated (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 33)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight, 1954-1956 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 34)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., Article, 1971 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 35)
  - Evans, Town of - Sesquicentennial, 1971 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 36)
  - F - General, 1953-1972 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 37)
  - Files - Information re: Frank C. Moore's Personal Files, 1969 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 38)
  - First World War Service - General, 1919-1965 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 39)
  - First World War Service - RFC & RAF, 1918-1936 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 40)
  - First World War Service - ROTC, 1917 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 41)
  - Fish, Ralph & Francis, 1969-1971 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 42)
  - Fleischmann Commission, Undated (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 43)
  - Fletcher, Dick & Ethel, 1971 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 44)
  - Forest Preserve, 1950-1964 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 45)
  - Freeman, Roger A., 1958-1969 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 46)
  - Froessel, Charles W., 1972 (Box 23 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 47)
  - G - General, 1955-1970 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Gardner, John, Undated (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Goldstein, Nathaniel, 1951-1952 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Golde, Max G., 1971-1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Governor Rockefeller Press Releases, 1971 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 5)
  - Governor's Press Releases, 1971-1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 6)
  - Goold, G. Howard, 1970 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Hallett, George, 1969-1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Hamilton County Investigation, 1949 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Hanks, Nancy, 1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Hanley, Joe - Campaign for Lieutenant Governor, 1943 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Harness Commission re: C. Russell Selkirk, 1971 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Harriman, Averell, 1959 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 13)
  - Harvard University - Overseers' Committee to Visit Graduate Schools, 1954-1955 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Health Insurance Plan (H.I.P), 1966 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Hennigan, Robery D., 1969 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 16)
  - Highways, 1954-1956 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Historical Association of New York State, 1956-1970 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Hobart College, 1943-1969 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Hobart & William Smith Colleges - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Hobart & William Smith Colleges - Reports & Bulletins, 1971-1973 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 21)
  - Hobart & William Smith Colleges - Reports & Bulletins, 1971 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Hurd, Dr. T. Norman, 1969 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 23)
  - I - General, 1959-1966 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 24)
  - Invitations, 1970-1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Invitations, 1972-1978 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 26)
  - K - General, 1951-1971 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 27)
  - Kassell, Mortimer M., 1957-1959 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 28)
  - Kenmore, Village of, 1933-1938 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Kenmore, Village of, 1958-1960 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 30)
  - King, Beecmer, 1971 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Kirchhofer, A.H., 1951 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 32)
  - Kushner, C.N., 1970 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 33)
  - L - General, 1958-1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 34)
  - Lanigan, Charles (Chairman, New York Republican State Committee), 1971 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 35)
  - Law, New York State Department of, 1955-1958 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 36)
  - League of Women Voters (Miscellaneous Chapters), 1957-1962 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 37)
  - Legislative Research, Office of, 1969-1970 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 38)
  - Legislative Resolution Mourning the Death of Frank C. Moore, 1978 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 39)
  - Legislature - General Information, 1963-1964 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 40)
  - Letters of Congratulation re: Appointment as President of Government Affairs Foundation, 1953 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 41)
  - Lieutenant Governor's Office - Resignation, 1953 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 42)
  - Lindsay, Mayor John, 1971; clippings (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 43)
  - Little Hoover Commission, 1960; clippings (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 44)
  - Local Governments - Taylor Law, 1972 (Box 24 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 45)
  - Lomenzo, Judge John P., 1962-1969 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Lottery - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Lottery - General, 1966-1967 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Lottery - News Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Lottery, New York State, 1972 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 5)
  - M - General (Folder 1 of 2), 1965-1969 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 6)
  - M - General (Folder 2 of 2), 1941-1963 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Macy vs. World Telegram & Sun, 1950 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Magazine Articles, 1959-1970 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Magazine Articles, 1959-1970 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Mandelbaum Act/WPA Bill, 1939 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Master Builder Lodge No. 911, 1952-1955 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Medal Collection, 1955-1965 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 13)
  - Memorial Hall, 1926-1932 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Military Service in Second World War, 1942 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1951-1969 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, Don, Undated (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Municipal Bonds, 1935-1968 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 18)
  - N - General, 1957-1969 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Natcharian, Naomi, 1970 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Natcharian, Naomi & Rose, 1970-1972 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 21)
  - National Association of Counties, 1972 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 22)